mishtalk.com 2016-11-06

# Mish’s Privacy Policy | MishTalk

Mish’s privacy policy pertains to all websites created or run by Mike “Mish” Shedlock” including but not limited to <https://mishtalk.com/> and its predecessor <http://globaleconomicanalysis.blogspot.com/>.

The word “Mish” in any of the following paragraphs means Mike “Mish” Shedlock” or any site run by Mike “Mish” Shedlock”.  
The words “we” or “our” in any of the following paragraphs, means Mish or anyone designated by Mish to act on behalf of Mish.

Mish alone can enter agreements with other parties or change this privacy policy.

### Terms of Use

You acknowledge that this Privacy Policy is also a part of our Site Terms of Use, and by accessing or using our site, you agree to be bound by all of its terms and conditions. If at any time you find these terms and conditions unacceptable, you must immediately leave the site and cease all use of the site.

### Information Collected

This site does not use cookies or collect any personal information other than email addresses of those signing up for email alerts.

Most of our advertising is served by third parties such as Investing Channel, Google Adsense, Amazon, and BitGold. All site advertisers, not just those mentioned, may use cookies or other technology to attempt to identify some of your preferences or retrieve information about you. Those cookies enable the advertiser to determine whether you have seen a particular advertisement before. Regardless of intent of any third-party cookies, Mish does not control their technology and is not responsible for any actions or policies of those parties.

Clicking on any link may take you to another site. When clicking on links that do take you to other sites, their privacy policy applies. Mish is not responsible for cookies or any actions of those sites.

### Confidentiality and Personal Information

We do not sell or give away any information that we collect except as required by law.

We may make use of chat rooms, forums, message boards, news groups, and various mechanisms for readers to make comments.

Please understand that any information that you disclose in such areas becomes public information. We have no control over its use and you should exercise caution when deciding to disclose your personal information.

### Emails and Submissions

If you send emails or submissions, we reserve the right to edit and publish those emails and submissions. We may use your name unless we receive explicit instructions, with each email or submission, to not use your name. In such cases, we reserve the right to use initials, made up names, and made up details so others cannot figure out who you are. You accept responsibility that our attempts to disguise who you are may not be perfect. Finally, if you are a public figure, we reserve the right to use your name whether or not permission is granted.

### Children Under the Age of 13

In compliance with Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act (“COPPA”), this site is not directed at children under the age of 13 and we do not intend to collect any personal identifiable information, such as name, home address, e-mail address, telephone number, or social security number, from children under the age of 13. If you are under the age of 13, please do not provide us with your personal identifiable information.

### Updates to Privacy Policy

We reserve the right, at any time and without notice, to add to, change, update, or modify this Privacy Policy, simply by posting such change, update, or modification on the Site and without any other notice to you. Any such change, update, or modification will be effective immediately upon posting on the Site.
